James R. "Jim" Dunnam papers, Inclusive: 1982-2011, Bulk: 1996-2010
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Legislative, 1982-2010; 4
  - 78th Session, 2001-2004, undated; 5
    - Topical, 2001-2004; 6
      - Congressional Redistricting TPS and Background (1 of 2), 2003 (Box 46, Folder 37)
      - Congressional Redistricting TPS and Background (2 of 2), 2003 (Box 46, Folder 38)
      - Corporal Punishment In Schools, 2001 November (Box 46, Folder 39)
      - Deferred Adjudication, 2003 March (Box 46, Folder 40)
      - Democratic Legislative Campaign Committee, 2001 November-December (Box 46, Folder 41)
      - Development, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 42)
      - Education Cuts, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 43)
      - Election, Court Petitions, 2004 November (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Energy, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Fire Fighter and Police Officer Home-Loan Program, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Focus Reports, 2004 March-April (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Gambling, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Health Insurance, 2004 June (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Health, State Health Institutions, 2004 July (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Home Equity, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Home Owners Insurance, 2002-2004 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Long-Term Nursing Care, 2002 November-December (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - Lottery, 2004 April (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - Office of Rural Community Affairs (ORCA), 2002 (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - On-Site Sewage Facilities Charge Back-Fee, 2002 July 17 (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - Open Meetings Act, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - OSFR Receipt of Federal Funds to Texas, 2003-2004 (Box 47, Folder 15)
      - Retention Elections, 2003 March 19 (Box 47, Folder 16)
      - School Financing, 2002 June (Box 47, Folder 17)
      - Tax Loop Holes, 2002 September (Box 47, Folder 18)
      - Teacher Retirement System Of Texas, 2002 May (Box 47, Folder 19)
      - Texas Association of Regional Councils, 2004 February-March (Box 47, Folder 20)
      - Texas Banking Laws, 2002 February 28 (Box 47, Folder 21)
      - Texas Department of Criminal Justice, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 22)
      - Texas District & County Attorneys Association, 2002 November (Box 47, Folder 23)
      - Texas Emerging Technology Fund, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 24)
      - Texas Engineering Practice Act, 2003 December (Box 47, Folder 25)
      - Texas Ethics Commission, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 26)
      - Texas State Technical College, circa 2002-2003 (Box 47, Folder 27)
      - Wrongful Termination By Insurance Companies, 2002 July (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - 79th Session, 2003-2007; 6
    - General, 2003-2006; 1
      - 72nd Session Bill History Report, 2004 November (Box 47, Folder 29)
      - Accomplishments, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 30)
      - Bill Search Results, 2005 January 25 (Box 47, Folder 31)
      - Dunnam Swearing-In, 2004 December (Box 47, Folder 32)
      - Newsletters (1 of 2), 2005 (Box 47, Folder 33)
      - Newsletters (2 of 2), 2005 (Box 47, Folder 34)
      - Photo Index of the 79th Legislature, circa 2005-2006 (Box 47, Folder 35)
      - Public Information Act Certificate of Course Completion, 2006 December 28 (Box 47, Folder 36)
      - Rules of the HOR, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 37)
      - State Finance Report, Fiscal, 2003-2005 (Box 47, Folder 38)
    - House Bills, 2005; 2
      - Bill Draft, School Funding Skeleton, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 39)
      - Bill Draft, Supplemental Salaries Paid To District Judges, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 40)
      - HB 1, General, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - HB 1, Amendments, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - HB 2, General (1 of 3), 2005 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - HB 2, General (2 of 3), 2005 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - HB 2, General (3 of 3), 2005 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - HB 2, Amendments (1 of 3), 2005 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - HB 2, Amendments (2 of 3), 2005 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - HB 2, Amendments (3 of 3), 2005 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - HB 3, General (1 of 3), 2005 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - HB 3, General (2 of 3), 2005 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - HB 3, General (3 of 3), 2005 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - HB 3, Amendments, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - HB 4, General, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - HB 5, Amendments, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - HB 72, Elderly and Disabled Tax Freeze Amendment, 2006 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - HB 326/SB 172, Offense Of Cruelty To Animals, Lobbying Materials For Amendments, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - HB 846, Payday Loans, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - HB 956, Composition Of The Juvenile Board Of Leon County, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - HB 1401, Franchise Tax Delaware Loophole, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - HB 1415, Violation Of Community Supervision, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - HB 1527, Breach In The Security Of A Data System That Includes Identifying Information (1 of 2), 2005 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - HB 1527, Breach In The Security Of A Data System That Includes Identifying Information (2 of 2), 2005 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - HB 2164, County Records Management And Preservation Fee, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - HB 2165, Sentencing Procedure In Capital Felony Cases, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - HB 3345, Creation Of The Texas Homefront Heroes Program, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - HB 3346, Issuance Of Order Of Nondisclosure With Report To Criminal History Records, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - HB 3347, Political Contributions And Expenditures, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 13)
      - HB 3348, Admitting Residents To Nursing Homes, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 14)
      - HB 3349, Lauren’s Law, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 15)
      - HB 3350, Duty To Report Child Abuse, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - HB 3351, Hotel Occupancy Tax (1 of 2), 2005 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - HB 3351, Hotel Occupancy Tax (2 of 2), 2005 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - HB 3352, Payday Loans, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Joint Resolutions, 2005; 3
      - HJR 100, Proposed Amendment Providing For Open Meetings (1 of 2), 2005 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - HJR 100, Proposed Amendment Providing For Open Meetings (2 of 2), 2005 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Commemoratives and Commendations, 2005; 4
      - HCR 185, Honorable Joe E. Moreno, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Topical, 2004-2007; 5
      - Alcohol Sunset Bill/Beer Tax, HB 2544, 2005 April-May (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - Alcoholic Beverage Code, 2004 December 28 (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - Building permits, HB 265, 2005 February 24 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - Cash For College, 2005 December 6 (Box 50, Folder 11)
      - Coal Electric Plant In Riesel, Texas, 2005 April-June (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - Coal-burning Plants, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 13)
      - Confiscation Of Private Property, 2005 June 27 (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - County Judges, SB 368, 2005 April-May (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - CPA License Fee, 2005 June 27 (Box 50, Folder 16)
      - Dental Hygiene, 2005 April 11 (Box 50, Folder 17)
      - Education, HB 2, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 18)
      - Education, HB 2, Democratic Caucus, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 19)
      - Electric Competition, SB 7, 2005 May 16 (Box 50, Folder 20)
      - Electricity, HB 1777, 2005 April 25 (Box 50, Folder 21)
      - Electricity Outsourcing, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 22)
      - Ethics Commission, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 23)
      - General Election Dispute In Calvert, Texas, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 24)
      - Government Assisted Programs In Oakwood, Texas, 2006 February-March (Box 50, Folder 25)
      - Handguns In Vehicles, HB 823, 2005 February-April (Box 50, Folder 26)
      - Health Care, circa 2005 (Box 50, Folder 27)
      - Helmet Law, HB 264, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 28)
      - Hochberg Alternative For Public Education, 2005 August 12 (Box 50, Folder 29)
      - Importation Of Prescription Drugs From Canada, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 30)
      - Job Incentive Programs, HB 2421, 2005 May 10 (Box 50, Folder 31)
      - John Paul II, HCR 139, 2005 April 22 (Box 50, Folder 32)
      - Judicial Compensation, CSSB 368, 2005 April 27 (Box 50, Folder 33)
      - Leon County Veterans Memorial, 2005 April-May (Box 50, Folder 34)
      - “Let Us Dream Together”, 2005 May 18 (Box 50, Folder 35)
      - Nursing Home Financing, 2005 June 7-9 (Box 50, Folder 36)
      - Office Of Rural Community Affairs (ORCA), 2005 June 24 (Box 50, Folder 37)
      - Pay Increase For DPS Officers, 2005 March 2 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Pay Increase For State Employees, 2005 March 3 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Payday Loans, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Payroll Tax, 2005 July 6 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Police Violence, 2005 July (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Privatization of Human Services System, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Property Tax, 2005 June 1 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - Protection Of Water Quality & Prevention Of Flooding, HB 2833/ SB 1647, 2005 April 28 (Box 51, Folder 8)
      - Public Utility Commission, 2006-2007 (Box 51, Folder 9)
      - Public Utility Commission, Report, 2005 January (Box 51, Folder 10)
      - Rollback Petition Requirements, HB 1006, 2005 April (Box 51, Folder 11)
      - Same-Sex Marriage, 2005 April-May (Box 51, Folder 12)
      - School Financing, 2005 June-July (Box 51, Folder 13)
      - School Vouchers, 2005 April-May (Box 51, Folder 14)
      - State Funded Lobbying Contracts (1 of 7), 2006 (Box 51, Folder 15)
      - State Funded Lobbying Contracts (2 of 7), 2006 (Box 51, Folder 16)
      - State Funded Lobbying Contracts (3 of 7), 2006 (Box 51, Folder 17)
      - State Funded Lobbying Contracts (4 of 7), 2006 (Box 51, Folder 18)
      - State Funded Lobbying Contracts (5 of 7), 2006 (Box 51, Folder 19)
      - State Funded Lobbying Contracts (6 of 7), 2006 (Box 51, Folder 20)
      - State Funded Lobbying Contracts (7 of 7), 2006 (Box 51, Folder 22)
      - State Health Insurance, 2005 March (Box 51, Folder 23)
      - State Tax, 2005 April 12 (Box 51, Folder 24)
      - Tarlton’s Amendment Disqualifying Gay, Lesbian, & Bisexual Foster Parents, SB 6, 2005 April-May (Box 51, Folder 25)
      - Tax On Reconstruction/Cosmetic Surgery, 2005 July 1 (Box 51, Folder 26)
      - Teacher Retirement System, 2005 April-August (Box 51, Folder 27)
      - Teacher Retirement System Health Insurance, 2005 March 10 (Box 51, Folder 28)
      - Telecommunications, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 29)
      - Texas Animal Health Commission (TAHC), 2006 January-March (Box 51, Folder 30)
      - Texas Lottery, 2005 July 16 (Box 51, Folder 31)
      - Texas Rangers, 2005 March 29 (Box 51, Folder 32)
      - Texas Workers’ Compensation System, 2005 April 21 (Box 51, Folder 33)
      - Trans Texas Corridor, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Trans Texas Corridor- 35, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Uniform Commercial Building Code, HB 1949, 2005 April 8 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Video Gambling (VLT’s), 2005 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Waco Center For Youth (WCY), 2005 June 22 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - 80th Session, 2004-2007; 7
    - General, 2007, undated; 1
      - Accomplishments of 80th Legislature, undated (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - Democratic Budget Priorities, 2007 March (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - “I Survived the 80th” Session T-Shirt, 2007 (Box 82 OVZ, Folder 3)
      - Opinion Analysis Poll, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - Potential Legislation, Legalize Cell Phone Jamming, 2007 February (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - Potential Legislation, Permitting Defensive Driving For CDL License Holder In Non-Commercial Vehicle, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - Potential Legislation, Worker’s Rights To Accrue Prorated Vacation Hours, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - True Courage For Protecting the Right to Vote, Framed Certificate, circa 2007 (Box 82 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - House Bills, 2007; 2
      - Bill Draft, Amendments, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - Bill Draft, Composition Of The McLennan County Juvenile Board, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      - Bill Draft, Texas Commission On Environment Quality Consideration Of The Cumulative Effects Of Emission, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 14)
      - Criminal Justice Bills, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 15)
      - HB 8, Amendments, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 16)
      - HB 12, Amendments, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 17)
      - HB 43, Prison Pay Telephone Service, Fiscal Note, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 18)
      - HB 45, Texas Department of Criminal Justice, Use of Tobacco Products, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 19)
      - HB 109, Amendments, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 20)
      - HB 427, Prosecution of Crimes Occurring in Texas Department of Criminal Justice or Texas Youth Commission, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 21)
      - HB 483, Homestead Exemption, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 22)
      - HB 626, Amendments, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 23)
      - HB 729, CHIP Restoration, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 24)
      - HB 928, Amendments, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 25)
      - HB 1596, Criminal Defendant Rights, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 26)
      - HB 1678, Community Supervision System, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 27)
      - HB 1875, Drug Court Programs, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 28)
      - HB 1875, Testimony, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 29)
      - HB 1888, Prison Pay Telephone Service, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 30)
      - HB 1888, Bill Analysis, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 31)
      - HB 1888, Fiscal Note, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 32)
      - HB 2006, Amendments, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 33)
      - HB 2053, Department of Criminal Justice, Sunset Amendments, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 34)
      - HB 2053, Sunset Recommendations, Fiscal Note, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 35)
      - HB 2103, Correctional Officer Scholarship Program, Bill Analysis, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 36)
      - HB 2103, Fiscal Note, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 37)
      - HB 2173, Amendments, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 28)
      - HB 2244, Officers to Prisoners Ratio, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 39)
      - HB 2340, Texas Youth Commission Conservatorship, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 40)
      - HB 2746, Texas Ethics Commission Internet Access To Filings, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 41)
      - HB 2938, Bill Analysis and Fiscal Notes, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 42)
      - HB 2938, Parole Dates, Bill Analysis, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 43)
      - HB 3206, Texas Youth Commission Sunset Review, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 44)
      - HB 3384, Texas Youth Commission Special Prosecutor, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 45)
      - HB 3426, Amendments, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 46)
      - HB 3655, Future Gen Protection Act, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 47)
      - HB 3656, Conditional Reduction Of Nitrogen Oxide Emissions, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 48)
      - HB 3657, Texas Commission On Environmental Quality Cumulative Effects Of Proposed Pollution Sources, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 49)
      - HB 3658, Leon County Hotel Occupancy Tax, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 50)
      - HB 3659, Prohibiting Disclosure Of Student’s Name In Improper Student Teacher Relationships, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - HB 3660, Robertson County Hotel Occupancy Tax, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - HB 3661, Governor’s Flag, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - HB 3662, Gubernatorial Instant Runoff Voting, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - HB 3663, McLennan County Hotel Occupancy Tax, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - HB 3664, Madison County Hotel Occupancy Tax, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - HB 3701, Texas Youth Commission Ombudsman, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - HB 3702, Mandatory Supervision for Drug Possession Offenses, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - HB 3928, Amendments, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - HB 3937, Triple Homestead Exemption, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - HB 3986/SB 1985, McLennan County Groundwater Conservation Act, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Senate Bills, 2007; 3
      - SB 3, Amendments, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - SB 482, Amendments, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - SB 483, Amendments, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 14)
      - SB909, Texas Department of Criminal Justice Sunset Bill, Testimonies, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Joint Resolutions, 2007; 4
      - HJR 4, Constitutional Amendment To Provide For Changing Gubernatorial Election To Instant Runoff Voting, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 16)
      - HJR 42, Homestead Exemption, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 17)
      - Resolution for 180-Day Moratorium on New Coal Plants, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Topical, 2004-2007; 5
      - CHIP Program and Bill Information, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 19)
      - Democratic House Leadership Joint State on SCR 20 Press Release, 2007 February 14 (Box 53, Folder 20)
      - Rep. Hopson Helps Pass Historic Property Relief Tax Press Release, 2006 May 12 (Box 53, Folder 21)
      - Texas Department of Transportation Lobbying Contracts Information, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 22)
      - Texas Youth Commission and State Auditor’s Audit Plan, 2004-2007 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - 81st Session, 2007-2010; 8
    - General, 2007-2010; 1
      - “The Bad Precedents” Hymnal, undated (Box 83 OVZ, Folder 1)
      - “The Bad Precedents” T-Shirt, Pink, circa 2007-2009 (Box 82 OVZ, Folder 5)
      - “The Bad Precedents” T-Shirt, Black, circa 2007-2009 (Box 82 OVZ, Folder 6)
      - Bill Forms, 2009 (Box 53, Folder 24)
      - Governor Rick Perry T-Shirt, 2009 (Box 82 OVZ, Folder 7)
      - Public Servant of the Year, Cen-Tex African American Chamber of Commerce, Plaque, 2010 October 26 (Box 82 OVZ, Folder 8)
    - House Bills, 2009; 2
      - Bill Draft, Approval By Texas Medical Board Of A Physician’s Website, 2009 (Box 53, Folder 25)
      - Bill Draft, Authority Of The Public Utility Commission Of Texas To Issue Certificates, 2009 (Box 53, Folder 26)
      - Bill Draft, County Fee On Registration Of A Vehicle To Fund Public Transportation, 2009 (Box 53, Folder 27)
      - Bill Draft, Nitrogen Oxides Emissions Reductions, 2009 (Box 53, Folder 28)
      - Bill Draft, Purchase Of Copper Parts, 2009 (Box 53, Folder 29)
      - Bill Draft, Requirements For A Certificate For Transmission Service, 2009 (Box 53, Folder 30)
      - Bill Draft, Temporary Increase In Amount Exempted From Ad Valorem Taxation By A School District, 2009 (Box 53, Folder 31)
      - Bill Draft, Voter Integrity, 2009 (Box 53, Folder 32)
      - HB 300, Amendments, 2009 (Box 53, Folder 33)
      - HB 300, Prohibition Tolling Pre-existing Roads, Bill Text, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - HB 565, Abolition Of The Texas Transportation Commission And Creation Of The Commissioner Of Transportation, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - HB 1366, Election Of The Governor, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - HB 2494, Child Support In Circumstances Of Mistaken Paternity, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - HB 2495, Cumulative Effects Of Emissions In Permit Processes, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - HB 2496, Posting Of Statements, Registrations, And Reports Filed With The Texas Ethics Commission On The Commissions Website, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - HB 2497, Conditional Reduction Of Nitrogen Oxides Emissions, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - HB 2498, Admission Of Sex Offenders As Residents Of Nursing Homes, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - HB 2499, Appropriation Of Money From Property Tax Relief Fund, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - HB 2500, Governor’s Flag, General, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - HB 2500, Bill Analysis, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - HB 2500, Bill Text, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - HB 2500, Fiscal Note, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - HB 2500, Talking Point, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 14)
      - HB 2701, Elected Commissioner, General, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 15)
      - HB 2701, Bill Analysis, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 16)
      - HB 2701, Bill Text, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 17)
      - HB 2701, Talking Point, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 18)
      - HB 2702, Adoption Of Rules Of Civil Procedures By The Supreme Court, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 19)
      - HB 2942, Fiscal Accountability And Transparency In Government Operations (1 of 3), 2009 (Box 54, Folder 20)
      - HB 2942, Fiscal Accountability And Transparency In Government Operations (2 of 3), 2009 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - HB 2942, Fiscal Accountability And Transparency In Government Operations (3 of 3), 2009 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - HB 3500, Municipal License Plate, General, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - HB 3500, Bill Analysis, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - HB 3500, Bill Text, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - HB 3500, Fiscal Note, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - HB 3500, Talking Point, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - HB 3509, Disqualification From Driving A Commercial Motor Vehicle, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - HB 3510, Protocol For Folding The State Flag, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - HB 3511, Making Of The Military Salute To The Texas Flag By Veterans, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - HB 3512, State Agency Information Available On The Internet, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - HB 3513, Duty To Protect And Safeguard Sensitive Personal Information, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 12)
      - HB 3515, BarraTry, General, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 13)
      - HB 3515, Bill Analysis, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      - HB 3515, Bill Text, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 15)
      - HB 3515, Talking Point, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 16)
      - HB 3578, Governor’s Mansion And Woodlawn (1 of 2), 2009 (Box 55, Folder 17)
      - HB 3578, Governor’s Mansion And Woodlawn (2 of 2), 2009 (Box 55, Folder 18)
      - HB 3582, Creation Of Emissions Database, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 19)
      - HB 3845, Designation Of Courthouse As A State Archeological Landmark, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 20)
      - HB 3964, Requirement That Physicians File Advertising With The Texas Medical Board, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - HB 3965, Exemption From Ad Valorem Taxation, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - HB 3966, Homestead Prorate, General, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - HB, 3966, Bill Text, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - HB 3970, Cable Bill, General, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - HB 3970, Bill Analysis, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - HB 3970, Bill Text, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - HB 3970, Fiscal Note, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - HB 3977, Surplus Of White-Tailed Deer, General, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - HB 3977, Bill Text, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - HB 4142, Copper Thefts, General, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - HB 4142, Bill Analysis, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      - HB 4142, Bill Text, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      - HB 4142, Talking Point, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 14)
      - HB 4418, Voter Integrity Act, General, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 15)
      - HB 4418, Bill Analysis, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 16)
      - HB 4418, Bill Text, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 17)
      - HB 4418, Fiscal Note, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 18)
      - HB 4418, Talking Point, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 19)
      - HB 4419, Secretary Of State, General, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 20)
      - HB 4419, Bill Analysis, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 21)
      - HB 4419, Bill Text, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 22)
      - HB 4419, Fiscal Note, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 23)
      - HB 4419, Talking Points, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 24)
      - HB 4420, Voter Cancellation, Bill Text, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 25)
      - HB 4421, Voter Registration Form & Info, General, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 26)
      - HB 4421, Bill Analysis, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 27)
      - HB 4421, Bill Text, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 28)
      - HB 4421, Fiscal Note, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 29)
      - HB 4421, Talking Point, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 30)
      - HB 4422, Voter Impersonation, General, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 31)
      - HB 4422, Bill Analysis, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 32)
      - HB 4422, Bill Text, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 33)
      - HB 4422, Talking Point, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 34)
      - HB 4444, Speaker Contributions, General, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 35)
      - HB 4444, Bill Analysis, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 36)
      - HB 4444, Bill Text, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 37)
      - HB 4444, Talking Point, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 38)
    - Senate Bills, 2009; 3
      - SB 362, Voter ID Bill, General, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 39)
      - SB 512, Authorizing The Department Of Public Safety To Establish A Driver Record Pilot Program, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 40)
      - SB 519, Child Support In Cases Of Mistaken Paternity, Bill Analysis, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 1)